

JOSE ANGEL RODRIGUEZ RAMOS

Autonomous City of Buenos Aires, Argentina

Mobile: +54-11-3957-7862 Mail: jrodriguez2076@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/jrodriguez2076 LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/jrodriguez2076

PERSONAL PROFILE

Electronic engineer with hands-on experience in Machine Learning and software development. Always willing to take on new challenges and expand my knowledge. A team player and very trainable. Will work hard and smart to reach the proposed goals.

SKILLS

- Javascript and Typescript
- Python
- Machine Learning
- NLP
- Bot Development
- MongoDB.
- Dart
- C, C++, and C#
- SQI
- PIC and Arduino-based Electronics development -Agile methodologies.

FRAMEWORKS

- -Angular 2+
- ReactJs
- Redux
- -NodeJS
- Flask
- Scrapy and Web Crawling
- Scikit Learn, Spacy and NLTK
- ASP.NET Core,
- Flutter for Mobile Development
- MERN Stack
- Scrum
- Kanban

WORK EXPERIENCE

MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER

Ernst & Young (EY) | Sept. 2019 - Present

- Bot Service implementation using Azure Cognitive Services
- Web Scrapping.
- Natural Language Processing and Machine Learning
- Python Backend Development.

AV/UC ENGINEER

Newtech Solutions Multimedia | Apr. 2018 - Present

- Bot Service implementation using Azure Bot Framework, Node.Js and .NET
- Conference room automation with proprietary frameworks, using C#
- Web Development, using Node.Js and React.js under Agile methodologies
- UI Development for corporate users, using React and Angular as frameworks

HOME AUTOMATION PROGRAMMER

Newcom LCS S.A. | Jun. 2017 - Apr. 2018

- Home Automation systems programming, using XML and C++ as core programming Languages, Following Agile Methodologies (Kanban)
- UI Layout development for home users, using React as framework

JUNIOR SYSTEMS PROGRAMMER

Audio Concept C.A. | Aug. 2015 - Nov. 2016

- Home Automation systems programming, using XML and C++ as core programming Languages

FREELANCER

Jun. 2018 - Present

- Web Apps Development Using different technologies:
 - Angular 2+, MERN Stack (MongoDB ExpressJS ReactJS NodeJS).
- Mobile App Development using Flutter

EDUCATION

UNIVERSIDAD SIMÓN BOLÍVAR Electronic Engineer, 2015. Caracas, Venezuela

COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

EducacionIT | 2018 | Node.Js and MongoDB Crestron Latin S.A. | 2018 | Foundations of Crestron Programming Microsoft | 2019 | Azure Fundamentals AZ-900 Udemy | 2020 | Python for Data Science & Machine Learning Udemy | 2020 | Hands On NLP using Python

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native English - Proficient Portuguese - Intermediate French - Elementary

OTHER SKILLS

- Proficiency to quickly learn new things
- Detail oriented
- Problem solver